I have a bad feeling about this there's
always a bigger fish does not make you
intelligent pilot my life your slave I'm
a person my name is Anakin no one can
tell a Jedi I wish that were so mom you
say the biggest problem in this universe
is nobody helps you each other may the
force be with you
he was your instincts remember
concentrate on the moment feel don't
think new is the path to the dark side
fear leads to anger anger leads to hate
hate leads to suffering your focus
determines your reality agree with you
the council does your apprentice
Skywalker will be always true there are
no more no less a master and an
apprentice the dark side clouds
everything impossible to see the future
base why do I get the feeling you're
going to be the death of me don't say
that master you're the closest thing I
have to a father attachments for me
possession is forbidden compassion which
I would define as unconditional love
central to a Jedi's life lost a planet
master obi-wan has young Skywalker
hey you're not all-powerful well I
should be some day I will be I will be
the most powerful Jedi ever it's all
though be ones foe
he's jealous he's holding me back
I killed them I killed them all and not
just the men
but the women and the children too
they're like animals and I slaughtered
them like animals the Shroud of the dark
side has fallen
begun the clone war has
I've got a bad feeling about this my
powers have doubled since the last time
we met count good twice the pride double
the fall death is a natural part of life
rejoice for those around you who
transform into the force mourn them do
not miss them do not attachment leads to
jealousy the shadow of greed that is
dark side of the force is a pathway to
many abilities some consider to be
unnatural is it possible to learn this
power
not from a Jedi obi-wan may the force be
with you
goodbye old friend may the force be with
the only through me can you achieve a
Power greater than any Jedi
I pledged myself to your teachings
henceforth you shall be known as da Veda
the time has come execute order 66
Master Skywalker there are too many of
them what are we going to do
so this is how Liberty dies it's under
supplies I have brought peace freedom
justice and security to my new empire
you were the chosen one it was said that
you would destroy the Sith not join them
bring balance to the force not leaving a
darkness you were my brother Anakin
I loved you
Loreena can you hear me yes master
you are part of the Rebel Alliance and a
traitor taken away just you reconsider
playing that message for him no I don't
think he likes you at all no I don't
like you either
for over a thousand generations the Jedi
Knights from the guardians of peace of
justice in the Old Republic before the
dark times before the Empire a young
Jedi named Darth Vader who was a pupil
of mine until he turned to evil helped
the Empire hunt down and destroy the
Jedi Knights he betrayed and murdered
your father
Vader was seduced by the dark side of
the force the force is what gives a Jedi
his path it's an energy field created by
all living things it surrounds us and
penetrates us it binds the Galaxy
together don't be too proud of this
technological terror you've constructed
the ability to destroy a planet is
insignificant next to the power of the
force I find your lack of faith
disturbing these aren't the droids
you're looking for the great disturbance
in the force as if millions of voices
suddenly cried out in terror and were
suddenly silenced I fear something
terrible has happened
hokey religions and ancient weapons are
no match for a good blaster at your side
kid
very bad feeling about lose them all
foolish fool or the fool who follows it
too short for a stormtrooper huh
Oh uniform I'm Luke Skywalker I'm here
to rescue you we meet again at last the
circle is now complete when I left you I
was but to learn now I am the master the
amount of evilness
you can't wind us if you strike me down
I shall become more powerful than you
can possibly imagine
hey Luke may the force be with you
evacuate in our moment of triumph I
think you overestimate their chances use
the Force
I thought they smelled bad on the
outside why you stuck-up half-witted
scruffy-looking nerf-herder who's
scruffy-looking the force is strong with
him the son of Skywalker must not become
a Jedi Adventure Jedi craves not these
things you are reckless
I'm not afraid you will be
you will be I feel cold
be strong the dark side of the force a
domain of evil it is and you must go now
no different only different in your mind
you must unlearn what you have feared -
I'll do not there is no try
sighs messagenet look at me that's me by
my size do you
hmm and where you should not for my Ally
is the force and Nepal for kite ISM
is why you fail apology accepted captain
needa that boy is our last hope
no there is a gardener I love you
I know the force is with you young
Skywalker but you are not a Jedi yet now
release your anger only your hatred can
destroy me oh don't make me destroy you
join me and I will complete your
training with our combined strength we
can end this destructive conflict and
bring order to the galaxy if you only
knew the power of the dark side obi-wan
never told you what happens in your
father he told me enough
I strongly Meyer with the force what we
start down the dark path forever will it
dominate your destiny your father was
seduced by the dark side of the force he
ceased to be Anakin Skywalker and became
Darth Vader when that happened the good
man who was your father was destroyed
lai lai is my sister the emperor has
been expecting you I know father so you
have accepted the truth I've accepted
the truth that you were once Anakin
Skywalker my father that name no longer
has any meaning for me you don't know
the power of the dark side I must obey
my master it's a drama your
overconfidence is your weakness your
faith in your friends is yours
I'm afraid the deflector shield will be
quite operational when your friends
arrive
with each passing moment you make
yourself more my servant you like your
father
for you that's betrayal father I feel
the good in you a conflict there is no
conflict and give yourself to the dark
side it is the only way you can save
your friends your feelings for them are
strong especially for sister if you will
not turn to the dark side then perhaps
she will never turn to the dark side you
failed your highness I am a Jedi like my
father before me so be it Jedi Luke help
me take this mask off I'll not leave you
here I've got to save you
already