I'm going to show the people of Gotham
their city doesn't belong to the
criminals in the corrupt people need
dramatic examples to shake them out of
apathy and I can't do that as Bruce
Wayne as a man of flesh and blood I can
be ignored I can be destroyed but as a
symbol
but a symbol I can be incorruptible I
can be everlasting what simple something
elemental something terrifying I'm
Batman
nice coat the idea was to be a symbol
that man
that was the point
if you're working alone wear a mask not
afraid to be seen standing up these guys
I'm asking out for you is to protect the
people you care about count to five then
throw
this blocks the remote detonator signal
to the ball get it onto it before
sunrise if I'd hit the button when it
starts when what starts or what is that
Beckham
I swear word of me from one professional
to another if you're trying to scare
somebody pick a better spot on this site
for wouldn't kill me
I'm counting on it who where are they I
don't know where he is he found us he
must have friends
where I Oh here ah
you're a guard made your kills for money
look if this man is everything that you
say he is
in the city what gives you the right
what's the difference between you and me
I'm not wearing hockey pads yeah who are
you pretending to be Bruce Wayne
eccentric really everybody I want to
thank you all for coming here tonight
and drinking all of my booze not really
there's a thing about being a Wayne that
you're never short of a few freeloaders
like yourselves to fill up your mansion
with so here's to you people thank you
that's enough
oh well no not finished taller you uh
all you phonies all you two-faced
friends you sycophant ik suck-ups
whoo smile through your teeth at me
please
leave me in peace please go stop smiling
it's not a joke please leave the party's
over
get out sir the pool is for decoration
and your friends do not have swimming
well I'm going to have to ask you to
leave it is not a question of money you
see I'm buying this hotel
and setting some new rules about the
pool area that's mr. Waynes now so
that's a very brave thing you did trying
to catch the light well you you weren't
protecting the van y-you know you think
I should go to the hospital you don't
watch a whole lot of news Steve mr. Winn
I believe in Harvey Dent I had to find a
way to stop them trying to kill me you
made a serious mistake I won't kill you
but I don't have to save him
you know it's you know how I got these
scars no but I know how you got me tell
me where the trash then you have my
permission to die are you doing what's
necessary my friend with a joke God
needs it's true
realtor hero or you live long enough to
see yourself become the villain I get no
sense as I'm not a hero I like that I
killed those people that's what I can be
no no you can't you're not I'm whatever
Gotham needs me to me
and the people know the hero who saved
them hero can be anyone even a man who
looks something as simple and reassuring
as putting a coat around young boys
shoulders to let him know the world and
you