we go good evening ladies and gentlemen
we are tonight's entertainment I only
have one question what happened to balls
drop off huh I'm gonna kill you what
would I do without you go back to
ripping off my dealers no no no no you
you complete me do I really look like a
guy with a plan because it's all part of
the plan evening commissioner C madness
as you know is like gravity all it takes
is a little push
I believe whatever doesn't kill you
simply makes you
stranger will fighting you I like that
let her go
very poor choice of words do you want to
know why I use a knife guns are too
quick you can't save her although little
emotion in you see in their last moments
people show you who they really are so
in a way I know your friends better than
you ever did
would you like to know which of them
were cowards let it go now what do you
watch
I just want my phone call
why so serious I thought my jokes were
bad
let's not blow this out of proportion
how about a magic trick I'm gonna make
this pencil disappear Donna it's gone if
you're good at something never do it for
free you see I like I have simple tastes
I enjoy dynamite and gunpowder and
gasoline
what's it and you know the thing that
they have in common they're a cheap
I'm only burning my half all you care
about is money this town deserves a
better classic and I'm gonna give it
dawn it's not about money it's about
something a message
everything burns
I'll you're mad they've work for me now
this is my setting it won't work why
don't we cut you up into little pieces
and feed you to your pooches hmm and
then we'll see how loyal a hungry dog
really is now our operation is small but
there's a lot of potential for
aggressive expansion so which of you
fine gentlemen would like to join our
team oh there's only one spot open right
now so we're gonna have tryouts make it
fast