we also wish to welcome our new Defense
Against the Dark Arts teacher professor
Dolores Umbridge and I'm sure you'll all
join me in wishing the professor good
luck
as usual our caretaker mr. Filch has
asked me to remind you
she was at my hearing
she works for fudge Thank You headmaster
for those kind words of welcome and how
lovely to see all your bright happy
faces smiling up at me I'm sure we're
all going to be very good friends that's
likely the Ministry of Magic has always
considered the education of young
witches and wizards to be of vital
importance although each headmaster has
brought something new to this historic
school Progress for the sake of progress
must be discouraged let us preserve what
must be preserved perfect what can be
perfected and prune practices that ought
to be prohibited
Thank You professor umbrage that really
was