oh yeah what up put it that way
I'm coming to the valley of peace it is
my great honor to present you tigress my
father trained monkey mantis the Furious
Five
warriors prepare wait nah Oh piggy home
ready for battle
well the thousand tongues of fire
and finally master tigress
believe me citizens you have not seen
anything yet I know the tigress face
iron axe and his blades of death I sense
the Dragon Warrior is among us citizens
of the Valley of Peace Master Oogway
will now choose the Dragon Warrior huh
Oh
what are you going what does it look
like I'm doing I'm going to see the
Dragon Warrior look I don't understand
you finally had the noodle dream I lied
I don't dream about noodles dad
oh come on son let's get back to work
okay
Oh
Oh what's good
where are you pointing oh okay sorry I
just wanted to see who the Dragon
Warrior was how interesting
Master are you pointing it me him who
you need the universe has brought us the
Dragon Warrior what what what
stop wait who told you to
waitwait that flabby panda can't
possibly be the answer to our problem
you were about to point a tigress and
that thing fell in front of her that was
just an accident
yeah no accident
forgive us master we have failed you
know if the Panda has not quit by
morning than I will have failed you