how's the family good that's my feeling
boy what up Larry coming down laughs you
okay now I realize that you guys you
probably heard about this other villain
who's all the pyramids apparently it's a
big deal people are calling it the crime
of the century and stuff like that what
am I upset
no I am NOT a little but we have had a
pretty good year ourselves and you guys
are all right in my bottle no no racist
look I'm going together needles why did
we do well we stole the Time Square
jumbo
but there's little we stole the Statue
of Liberty
a small one from Las Vegas I won't even
mention the Eiffel Tower
also Vegas okay I wasn't going to tell
you about this yet but I have been
working on something very big something
then more this pyramid thing out of the
water and thanks to the efforts of my
good friend dr. Nefario thank you
stylin now we have low pay in a secret
lab and once we taste shrink lay we will
have the capability to pull off the
throw line of the century we are going
to steal
wait wait I haven't told you what it is
hey Dave listen up please
next we are going to steal
is mine involved will give me what
Mack and I will be the greatest villain
of all time that's what I'm talkin bout