it's show time
all right everyone chill allow me to
break the ice I need your clothes your
boots and your motorcycle
I did nothing the pavement was his enemy
Dylan you son of a bitch listen to me
very carefully you are not you you're me
no shit
You Know Who I am I've seen you before
you're the asshole on TV right wrong now
to ask you a bunch of questions now want
to have them answered immediately oh why
should I
because I'm going to say please drop
dead
I don't do requests for you Connie you
got a lot of nerve showing your face
around your house er and Cruz talking
from lapsing before wins you're a funny
guy Sully I like you that's why I'm
going to kill you last what you been
feeding this thing blonds come on don't
bullshit me bullshit shit bullshit
bullshit bullshit oh Jesus you're gonna
kill that guy
of course I'm a terminator I suppose
nothing hurts you only pain
talk to the hand
give us the girl are well-taken enough
talk into the boat in the tunnel to the
chopper you did not make it Victor
sweetheart we're married consider that a
divorce hello cutie-pie
one of us is in deep trouble I'm regnant
it might be a tumor it's not a tumor
it's not a tumor at all chill out
dickwad stop cheering me up no problemo
this for sleeping with my wife the damn
minivan grant me revenge and if you do
not listen
then the hell with you the hell with you
hell you will
who the hell are you my name is John
Kimble and I love my car
you shouldn't I'm not shooting on your
hey you want to be a farmer
here's a couple of acres here cool off
yeah stick around let me stop give you a
lift
you're fired your luggage you are stupid
I ask that guy Kona phrase
well that hit the spot to be or not to
be not to be the Iceman Cometh
hey like that hey Christmas tree me yeah
I'm gonna make it part of you yep
keep it what happened to Gaza ah you
have to split doesn't anyone say trade
anymore
this is war let's kick some ice crush
your enemies see them driven before you
they hear a lamentation of the women goo
da da ball if you please we can kill it
now this is the plan get your ass to
Mars good late traffic may I see your
invitation please sure here's my
invitation what killed the dinosaurs
yeah hey frosty Mac Mac Mac Mac Mac Mac
Mac Oh Steel God doesn't want you to go
in there and go in there when the guard
should have killed my dog you should
clone yourself Martha so you can go fuck
yourself she's dead you lie I'm not a
pervert I just was looking for turbo man
doll you want a turbo man for Christmas
forget it I'm not gonna sit the new lab
bring the toy back bring the toy back to
the carpet bring it back to the carpet
to get toy back to the carpet they do
toy back to the carpet they get back the
first time in my life I'm pissed off
give me the goddamn plate my life is not
crazy nah bet no I don't stop it I want
my baby Shh but I'm all woman my nipples
are very sensitive feel how soft my skin
is I want man Larry I don't want to see
you stop being such a pussy I can shut
me just a scratch I do not want to touch
his ass I want to make him talk okay
make it quick those men was getting
tired this hero stuff is spinach I need
a vacation
oh shit
shit shit shit God going to play a
wonderful game called
who is your daddy and what does he do
I'm a cybernetic organism living tissue
over metal endoskeleton come with me if
you want to live who are you the famous
comedian Arnold braunschweiger dangers
betrayed I can break your neck like a
chicken's you're mine now
you belong to me you're not gonna have
your mommies from behind you anymore
wipe your little douches no more
complaining no more mr. Kimble have to
go to the bathroom nothing there is no
bathroom shut up shut up shut up shut up
you should not drink and bake fuck you
fuck you fuck you fuck you asshole fuck
you asshole fuck you asshole as a
fucking asshole assholes dickheads come
back slots 5.1 ugly motherfucker what a
hell are you the fuck are you this is
Marge what the fuck yoke of my cabin he
molested murdered and mutilated her cool
introducing our ba da da da da da this
is a baton it's a SARS fighting Tamia's
coming is there having sex with a woman
and coming Lotus for babies when you go
up if the Bethea freeze in hell bad
you killed my father big mistake
you've just been erased you are
terminated see the party Richter please
well excuse me
don't disturb my friend he's dead time
can't do that the governor gets here
call me does the Green Berets gonna kick
your big ass all right it's Green Berets
for breakfast right not very hungry
I've seen those movies where they say
make my day I'm your worst nightmare
well listen to this one rubber baby
buggy bumpers ha ha
you think this is the real Quaid it is
you're not sending me to the cool
I kept my orders yeah yeah I'm a police
officer
this is an arrest freeze jeez I'm a cop
you idiot
I'm detective John Kimble these men is
under arrest cocaina so who you met yeah
I'm the party pooper remember Sally when
I promised to kill you last that's what
made you did I lied no sequel for you
I'll be back I'll be back I'll be back
I'm back get down get down get down get
down get down get down get down get down
I'll put you down get out get out get
out get out
hasta la vista baby
little some steam Bennett here is top
zero now plane zero leave anything for
us just bodies come on go Hagen you got
what you want give this people air do it
do it come on kill me I'm here come on
do it now
hmm oh this goggies but then cook it
down now you want to fuck with me you
think you know bad huh
you're fucking choirboy compared to me a
graboid
you call splatters bastard I'll tell you
what I think of it I live to see you eat
that contract but I hope you live in a
room for my fist because I'm going to
ram it into your stomach and break you
got them spine