I'm old not obsolete old not obsolete
old and not obsolete not yet listen to
me very carefully I want to ask you a
bunch of questions I want to have them
answered immediately oh why should I
because I'm going to say please what do
you think you're going
sure the captain gave you permission
careful this goes very vicious never on
this ship you don't I get your carcass
below get yours give me the damn finger
let me ever go before I change my mind
and write a citation you are not you
you're me no shit you became alright
everyone chill allow me to break the ice
I did nothing
the pavement was his enemy I need your
clothes your boots and your motorcycle
yeah you're closed give them to me now
take off your clothes
your clothes you won't be needing any
clothes drop dead
I don't do requests for you Connie you
got a lot of nerve showing your face
around your house err and crews talking
from laps if you're for wins you're
funny guy Sully I like you that's what
I'm going to kill you last what you been
feeding this thing mom's the only
problem I've got is that I'm doing you a
job you should be cleaning up the paint
you should be reading stories about PS
that go shopping please have a penis
girls have a vagina thanks for the tip I
just hold your lunches you mean you'd
other people's lunches stop it how'd it
go go oh I suppose nothing hurts you
only pain
talk to the hand enough walk into the
boat into the tunnel to the chopper
you did not make it Victor the fun
sweetheart
we're married consider that a divorce
hello cutie-pie
one of us is in deep trouble
pregnant it might be a tumor it's not a
tumor it's not a tumor at all chill out
dickwad oh stop cheering me up
no problemo that's for sleeping with my
wife the damn minivan grant me revenge
and if you do not listen then the hell
with you
the hell with you the hell you will put
how are you my name is John Kimble and I
love my car you know I've seen you
before you're the asshole on TV hey you
want to be a farmer here's a couple of
acres here
screwed off yeah stick around from the
star give you a lift
you're fired
your luggage you are a stupid I ask that
guy Kona phrase
well that hit the spot to be or not to
be not to be the Iceman Cometh
hey like that hey Christmas tree me yeah
I'm gonna make your party you
keep it what happened to Gaza ah he had
to split doesn't anyone say trade
anymore this is war
let's take some ice Russia enemies see
them driven before you they hear a
lamentation of the women right wrong
wrong I did not kill him in your dreams
do dah dah bah she bleeds we can kill it
now this is the plan
get your ass to boss where the hell were
you stuck in traffic
good late traffic may I see your
invitation please sure here's my
invitation see at the party Richter what
killed the dinosaurs yeah he's a frosty
Mack Mack Mack Mack Mack Mack Mack Mack
Mack hey crow yes Oh steel God doesn't
want you to go in there go in there when
the guard should have killed my dog you
should clone yourself Martha so you can
go fuck yourself I'm not a pervert I
just was looking for Tom Ament doll you
want a turbo man for Christmas forget it
I'm not gonna sit in your lap you
shouldn't I'm not shitting on you you've
gotta be shitting me
I am NOT shitting you come on don't
bullshit me bullshit bullshit bullshit
bullshit oh Jesus you're gonna kill that
guy of course I'm a terminator bring the
toy back bring the toy back to the
carpet bring it back to the carpet did
you talk back to the carpet they get toy
back to the carpet they get back the
first time in my life I'm pissed off
give me the goddamn place my name is not
crazy no bet no I don't stop it I want
my baby Shh but I'm all woman my
neighbors are very sensitive feel how
soft my skin is I want man Larry I don't
want to see you I do not want to touch
his ass I want to make him talk okay
make it quick because my voice is
getting tired this hero stuff is spinach
I need a vacation oh shit shit shit shit
shit God going to play a wonderful game
called who is your daddy and what does
he do I'm a cybernetic organism living
tissue over metal endoskeleton come with
me if you want to live who are you the
famous comedian Arnold braunschweiger it
is nice to meet you
dangers betrayed temper
I can break your neck like a chicken
you're mine now you belong to me
you're not gonna have your mommies from
behind you anymore wipe your little
douches no more complaining no more mr.
Kemp left to go to the bathroom nothing
there is no bathroom shut up shut up
shut up shut up you should not drink and
bake no fucking way
fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you
asshole fuck you asshole fuck you
asshole guys a fucking asshole assholes
dickheads come back at slots 5.1 ugly
motherfucker what a hell are you the
fuck I Jesus Marge what the fuck y'all
got my kebab I know you your mother she
was my favorite whore in Marrakesh and
she could polish a helmet clue reason
you killed my father
big mistake you've just been erased you
are terminated please well excuse me
don't disturb my friend he's dead tired
oh the governor gets here call me the
Green Berets gonna kick your big ass all
right Green Berets for breakfast right
not very hungry
see those movies where they say make my
day I'm your worst nightmare well listen
to this one rubber baby buggy bumpers ha
ha you think this is the real Quaid it
is units any needle cool I have my
orders drop the gun yeah I'm a police
officer this is an arrest
freeze jeez I'm a cop you idiot I'm
detective John Kimble this man is under
arrest who the hell are you
I'm the sheriff so who you meant shit
I'm the party pooper Koga II know he
said that you'd let me go I lied
remember Sally when I promised to kill
you last that's what made you did I lied
you lie I'll be back I'll be back I'll
be back I'll be back I'll be back I'll
be back I'll be back I'll be back and
back I'm back get down get down get down
get down get down get down get down get
down
I'll put you down get out get out get
out get out
hasta la vista baby
little some steam Bennett here is top
zero now plane zero leave anything for
us just bodies come on go Hagen you got
what you want give this people air do it
do it come on kill me I'm here
come on do it now don't blow your balls
off okay don't worry they made of brass
are they as big as your wives
hmm Oh cookies but they cook it down
now mr. Joseph T Brenner what's a piece
dead pussy
that is a very immature response good
morning
could I speak to the drug dealer of the
house please I beg your pardon
it's a beautiful day and be out killing
drug viewers at the N in the house in
material luggage just him let's do it
one more time let's not don't you know
the building is on fire this place looks
like a fucking crack house my CPU is in
Rouen that process a learning computer
have you ever killed anyone
yeah but they were all bad makes you a
murderer this is all a lie I was framed
I'm completely innocent let me be the
judge of that I am tired of the same old
faces the same old things
I'm the mercenary nobody pays me and if
I think somebody owes me something I
take it my name is fries varied well
what's the chilling sound of your doom
murder one this time now you're mine
what are you my father she goes with us
she's too valuable
so give away our position any chance she
gets No Deal you're still under orders
major
she's your baggage you fall behind and
you're on your own
where are you going over there what for
to show them all the sauce it is cause
you're police officers
not politicians give me the dog box no
well this is solar actually talk about
male and female animals
holy moly you ain't got no money
Nicholas doesn't need any money isn't it
enough sin Hercules loading your chariot
give Ben a model list drop dead you
asshole
I'm unable to comply
i brakes underground complex underground
you guys don't shut up I'm going to
uplink you ask you'll be on the ground
you don't stop screwing around back yeah
this is what I'm gonna do with you I'm
gonna throw up all over you
go ahead won't your this shirt a laundry
service that delivers Wow my government
does not like to do laundry in public
because I'm not into politics having to
survival my body my choice between your
faith in my Glock 9-millimeter I take my
clock if you drop your gun now the
promise I won't kill you who do you
think I look like Dirty Harry who is
dirty Hari take off your sunglasses
who's asking the Tin Man I'm a friend of
Sarah Connor trust me
stay thy hand fair prince who said I'm
fair but those on or I will call it a
favor okay
ah
that's a flavor sometimes famous world
you had me cloned yes or you cloned the
wrong man we're not afraid to die good
because I'm not afraid to kill all by
the light don't forget to send me a copy
don't give up your day job don't do that
I'm afraid they're big conditioners left
me close to your pleas of mercy just
kill that son of a bitch when I had the
chance did you put a shirt on what is
the name of the demon ADA who gave him
permission to pretend to be Hercules
insolence if I'm not me who the hell am
i with your eyes in here
no one can take that from you if you
yield only to a conqueror then prepare
to be conquered your confusion is not
rational she's a healthy female of
breeding age is that the big something
big yours give a permit for that monster
oh this is embarrassing
you've no respect for logic I have no
respect for those with no respect for
logic
guys want to get a room we got moving
room but you're not gay Oh baby
nice night for a walk nice night for a
walk the only two people left in the
world Adam and Eva where do you just
stop all this church talk and tell us
what the hell is going on the hell is
going on here there's someone in my
house eating my birthday cake with my
family and it's not me what the fuck did
I do wrong I wasn't fucking there hail
that son of a bitch who fuck you and me
this all fucking hell is gonna break
loose
hey mister walk your talk I can hear my
dog I cannot watch it you're damaged
goods lady god damn your brand I want
you to go to hell gamma Network Internet
bro that's right Jamie debiasse forget
this crazy applic business you're gonna
get us all killed
why I saved a life today what the hell
did you do this psychopathic bitch all
right
you did like a vegetarian joy we can do
better than that he didn't disappear he
was skinned alive and my orders were to
get somebody who could crack these
bastards so cooked up a story and drop
the six of us in a meat grinder mother
you killed my father
you killed my cancer you took my
father's sword ah it's a cold towel
Thanks did you see snakes magic Magnum
anything else
Lucy 9-millimeter knives and stabbing
weapons what's the matter
the CIA got you pushing too many pencils
how are you doing our fare in the water
swimming was an explosion
Oh for cheer shit I remember tastes like
this and the father took me to the
forest in v8 wild blueberries stop being
such a pussy revenge is a dish best of
cold it's time to face say breakfast is
the most important meal of the day I put
a sock in it I don't care who does water
your Hershey Highway and stop shouting
I'm not deaf come on
stop whining but you're still an idiot
what's your name
calculus sir so ed and democratic you're
addressing the captain of the ship now
you say sir to me
I'm Hercules so you told me no man is
superior to Achilles eighteen credits
please sue me dickhead gotta promise me
you're not gonna kill anyone right John
Connor talks too much
ah he'll live
what'd you do with Sully I let him go
they caught a train when I say you
should screw yourself
I didn't mean for you to take it
literally Dylan you son of a bitch that
idea come on back
it's party ah you have striped Hercules
I gotta get me outta your doctor you're
dead no you're dead
try to stay there this time can you be
cold Batman when you're going to kill me
now no sequel for you it's just at all
it's just a stupid little plastic doll
dog he got cold
Oh
yeah
stay you believe that that you before
you picked the wrong day you started it
this is not a dog this is a ferret very
that's a period fine jet but VLC horses
get off
there's the seal twice come on come on
come on come on come on come on come on
come on
come on come on come on baby Oh the
bridges it's
oh please anything but my statue of me
she did you make a movie mistake
you forgot to reload the damn gun say
goodbye Josh yeah goodbye
terminated alright enough philosophy I
better get going it's the last time last
time introducing ave da da da da da
this is Abaddon it's a SARS Fang to me
as the coming is they're having sex with
a woman and coming Lorna's for babies
when you go up if the vampyre you want
to fuck with me you think you know bad
huh
you're fucking choirboy compared to me a
quiet boy you cold-blooded bastard I'll
tell you what I think of it I live to
see you eat that contract but I hope you
live in a room for my fist because I'm
going to Ram it into your stomach and
break your goddamn spine