what am i you're my son
what more not I am Loki of Asgard and I
am burdened with glorious purpose no
peace brother of Thor we have no quarrel
with your people an ant has no quarrel
with a boot so you know one who showed
us the way into Asgard has it's a bit of
fun raining
to ruin my brother's big day and to
protect the realm from his idiotic rule
for a while longer if I had not taken
you in you would not be here now to hate
me if I'm free asking for mercy stay
just swing it it's not that I don't love
our little talks it's just I don't love
him you know it all makes sense now
why you favorite for all these years
because of my how much you claim to love
me even an hour of frost giants enable
the throne of Asgard
[Music]
it's the unspoken truth of humanity that
you crave subjugation you were made to
be ruled in the end you will always
kneel loki is it breezy everyone was
doing are you mad
possibly
- okay
[Music]
what happened he want to tell you so
salt
don't tell me what I want what maybe the
ribbon is here I'll pay her a minute
myself to have the tesseract have power
unlimited and for what a warm lifelong
and kind of share and then to be
reminded what real power is