celebrate your birthday by infiltrating
the United States gold depository at
Fort Knox fun what there she is boys
you have ejected and the holy desires
yet what's our rule about interrupting
analogies sorry please continue the
moments gone
private ruined it sir we're approaching
our target galovski sorry sir no clue
[Music]
Dave sorry wait wait I I live this way
go ahead and continue you seriously
don't remember me
Dave Dave right oh yeah a long time uh
that's a wife I've never been married
you may not remember we're not going
anywhere with you we do know that you
are the north wind is an elite
undercover industry the north wind is an
elite I'm an elite undercover
interspecies task force dedicated to
help help
okay dedicated to that dedicated to
helping animals and can't stop
themselves like penguins
really as you are my name is classified
classified a what is that Dutch can't
really hear the accent excuse me there's
the accent my name is a classic just
tell me everything you know all right
never trust a Dutchman in a tulip thing
sugar Canada secretly training an army
of Sasquatch not jugs in fact only 70%
actual does know everything everything
just everything regarding your abduction
by dr. Octavius brine ah what if say sir
what my team isn't kept that dr.
Octavius brine is actually an individual
known as Derrick Dave as Dave precisely
that's exactly what our Intel indicated
[Applause]
but what you of course could not know is
that dr. Brian's laboratories Venice is
secretly developing a doomsday weapon
called the Medusa serum is that dirt
Dave Dave won't be using his bazooka
seer Medusa serum Medusa serum on
anybody that part is accurate
John Rico
Dave Dave he hacked into our system
where's the sound hey Dave your
microphone is it's not on the button
with the picture of the microphone with
the picture of the microphone I'm a
billion calls end this happened but now
we can hear you buddy every week a Nazi
nine that's like talking to my parents
[Applause]
too sweet he does we must be on a plane
what did north wind do to us oh they
gave us badges not bad just tranquilizer
darts classified that lowdown dirty dog
is trying to kick us off the mission he
thinks we can't save the Penguins
because we're just well penguins are our
flesh and feathers they're us and if
anyone's gonna save us
but skipper we've gotta be five miles up
pretty much limits our options I make my
own options outside to pick up the slack
[Music]
okay plus where does this aircraft go
from the odd shape of this bagel
I'd say we're headed from Paris France
plus where does this aircraft go from
the odd shape of this bagel
I'd say we're headed for Paris France
forget it
not with their tax laws then I would
suggest a mid-air transfer bingo there's
our ride boys can't stay down dangerous
man this juice
[Music]
we're skipper
Oh private stop playing with those
backpacks like something useful now
we're talking let's get to work
400 meters 300 meters take American
Kowalski 218 yards 109 yards ok then
let's play what we need to do next first
word two syllables sounds like sounds
like sounds like like what starts with
here
[Music]