want to know why lucky let us take him
he's not leading an army from here I
don't think we should be focusing on
love that guy's brain is a bag full of
cats he could smell crazy on him I've
care how you speak loki's beyond reason
but he's about God and he's my brother
he killed 80 people in two days he
doctored
[Applause]
[Music]
you're no match for the mighty not meant
for mortal men neither was Omaha Beach
blondie stop trying to scare us all
right
egg shell shear I accept your surrender
[Applause]
anyone else Joe big fort bigger whore
status the girl tried to walk my mind
take special care I got a human to keep
her faith fortunately I am mighty
why don't each other I accepted Astoria
to kill our friends to kill me why must
have been forcing far Larkin I'm a
talented liar brother always help me
it's good to have you back lucky turn
off the cataract or I'll destroy you
can't there is no stopping it
there is only the war so be it
I will protect our garden all the realms
with my last every breath but I cannot
do so from that chair
Loki for his grave imbalance understood
rulers I know I never will the brutality
the sacrifice it changes you I'd rather
be a good man than a great king I turned
that key and drop this rock a little
early and it's still billions dead how
many you can't stop that I am Thor son
of owned as long as there is life in my
breasts
I am running out of things to say are
you ready
[Music]