it is time you here to kill me
[Music]
no you must live I'm a cybernetic
organism living tissue over metal
endoskeleton my mission is to protect
you yeah who sent you you did 35 years
from now you reprogrammed me to be your
protector here this time
[Music]
I cannot I cannot kill Sarah Connor I'm
a friend of Sarah Connor I was told that
she's here good Seop now can't be
explained in statement where she look
may take a while why wait this bench
over there
I'll be back sure about it but her and
me and me your confusion is not rational
she's a healthy female of breeding age
it is a little more to it than that my
database does not encompass the dynamics
of human peer pounding then you should
be able to baited calories in this
timeline okay we're not having a
conversation again we know that your son
will be John Connor and that the
machines cannot be defeated without him
I do not see a choice
story of my life look and it's not just
mating I'm supposed to fall in love with
him my files to look buted we're not
gonna make it
people I mean it's in your nature to
destroy yourselves no no no you
shouldn't even exist we took out
Cyberdyne over ten years ago we stopped
jogging today the only postpone that
judgement day is inevitable
your clothes give them to me
now fuck you asshole you won't be
needing any clothes
I've been waiting for you my are you
doing
nautical I don't know why you cry
that is something I can never do
you
[Music]