Prime!
Stop! No!
I am Bumblebee, your oldest friend.
Optimus,
I would lay down my life for you.
Bumblebee. Your voice.
I have not heard it
since cybertron fell.
What have I done?
You blew your chance to kill unicron.
I knew you couldn't do it.
Your time is over, prime.
You failed.
You turned your back on cybertron.
Now you will watch earth die.
No!
Not going so well.
Cade!
You betrayed your own kind.
No, prime, get up!
You chose the wrong side.
The guardian knights
are going to kill me.
Quintessa is the great deceiver!
The judgment is death.
Cade, I have failed you.
I have doomed earth.
Earth, the only place in the universe
whose people let me call it
home.
Only you can make it right, prime.
I can't do it without you.
One moment, that's all we got.
It's up to you, prime.
Because without you,
we all die.
It's now or never.
My brothers,
I will never betray you again.
I am optimus prime.
To save earth, we must go to cybertron
and destroy quintessa.