gotta make it stop I can't take it
anymore
I've eaten things that didn't complain
this much you were meter holding it
wrong just head just put it down come up
from there McMenamin ringing in its nose
as dry that means something's wrong with
it
someone should lick it just in case I'll
do it hey he's wearing one of those baby
thingies so so if he poops where does it
go
humans are disgusting okay you check for
poo hey why am I the poop checker was
returning the runt was your idea because
you're small and insignificant and
because I'll pummel you if you don't why
else
now SID I mean my goodness
alright look out look out coming through
watch out stop waving that thing around
fufu I'm gonna slip huh
got you will you cut it out hey do that
again he likes it
it's making me feel better to turn them
towards me the baby there he is
where's the baby
there is stop it you're scaring home
I bet he's hungry
how about some milk oh I'd love some not
you the baby well I ain't exactly
lactating right now pal you're a little
low on the food chain me mouthing off
you