it's finally ready yeah you know I went
through quite a few supers to get it
worthy to fight you but man it wasn't
good enough
after you trash the last one I had to
make some major modifications sure it
was difficult but you are worth it hey
after all I am your biggest fan Buffy my
name is not bi and it's not incredible
either that ship has sailed all I wanted
was to help you I only wanted to help
and what did you say to me fly home
buddy I work alone it tore me apart but
I learned an important lesson you can't
count on anyone especially your heroes
I was wrong to treat you that way I'm
sorry see now you respect me because I'm
a threat that's the way it works turns
out there are a lot of people whole
countries who want respect and they will
pay through the nose to get it how do
you think I got rich I invented weapons
and now I have a weapon that only I can
defeat and when I unleash a
you sly dog you got me monologue that's
cool huh zero-point energy yeah I saved
the best inventions for myself
she was super I'm single
your nemesis in it brilliant