doesn't have to get any message of
course it does
I've come too far for anything else I am
Loki of Asgard and I am burdened with
glorious purpose Loki brother a sword we
have no qualms with an ant has no
quarrel with a boot you planning to step
on us I come with glad tidings of a
world made free free from what freedom
freedom is life's great lie once you
accept that your heart
[Music]
is not this simpler is this not your
natural state
if the unspoken truth of humanity lets
you crave subjugation the bright lure of
freedom diminishes your life's joy in a
mad scramble for power her identity you
were made to be ruled in the end you
were always
it's an impressive case not built I
think for me look for something a lot
stronger then you know I've heard -
beast man how desperate are you you call
on such lost creatures to defend you how
desperate am i you threaten my world
with war you steal a force you can't
hope to control you talk about peace and
you kill cause it's fun you have made me
very desperate you might not be glad
that you did to have the tesseract to
have power unlimited
and then to be reminded what real power
is
[Music]
creature