Children, are you okay?
The same camp Guess who. Hello, I
Hey, man. - Yes
It was horrible - yes ah
You done it, okay?
what? I'm fine, I'm fine. - you do well. stay
No, well I've got to get him back
You want to go home, or I'll call Aunt May!
Dude. - You done it!
Wait!
Mr. Stark, and so on. I did not finish my ...
Well, I've done I've had enough.
I said I would help you find him, not catch him.
There were two
I am sorry.
me too
As I said,
disaster.
Visual hallucinations, there is a villain in my six o'clock direction
Visual hallucinations! You receive?
His aim propeller, turning him into a glider
Rhodes!
Tony, I lost the momentum
Read living index
Heartbeat is detected.
Emergency medical is on the way.
I am sorry