Oh Master Shifu ah you think this is
funny
Tai Lung has escaped from prison and
you're acting like children what he is
coming for the dragon scroll and you are
the only one who can stop him and Here I
am saying you got no sense of humor
I'm gonna stop then what you're serious
and I have to I know Master Oogway
you'll stop him he did it before I'll do
it again
dude we cannot not anymore our only hope
is the Dragon Warrior the Panda that's
the Panda Master please let us stop Tai
Lung this is what you've trained us for
no it is not your destiny to defeat Tai
Lung
it's his where'd he go you cannot leave
a real warrior never quits
watch me oh come on how am I supposed to
beat Tai Lung I can't even beat you to
the stairs you will beat him because you
are the Dragon Warrior ow
you don't believe that oh you never
believed that from the first moment I
got here you've been trying to get rid
of me yeah I was but now I asked you to
trust in your master as I have come to
trust in mine you're not my master and
I'm not the Dragon Warrior then why
didn't you quit you know I was trying to
get rid of you yet you stayed yeah I
stayed I stayed because every time you
threw a brick at my head
or said I smelled it hurts but it could
never hurt more than it did every day of
my life just being me
I stayed because I thought if anyone
could change me could make me not me it
was you the greatest kung fu teacher in
all of China but I can't change you I
can turn you into the Dragon Warrior and
I will come on
Tai Lung is on his way here right now
and even if it takes him a hundred years
to get here how are you gonna change
this into the Dragon Warrior huh
how how how I don't know
I don't know
that's what I thought