there's not many people who can sneak up
on me but you figured I'd come after
after whatever tortures fury can concoct
you would appear as a friend as a bomb
and I would cooperate I want to know
what you've done to agent Barton I'd say
I've expanded his mind once you've won
once you're king of the mountain what
happens to his mind there's this love
agent Romanoff love is for children I
owe him the death tell me before I
worked for shield I
well I made a name for myself I have a
very specific skill set I didn't care
who I used it for or on I got on shields
radar in a bad way
hatred Barton was sent to kill me he
made a different call
and what will you do if I vow to spare
him not let you out on that but I like
this your world in the balance and you
bargain for one man regime is fall every
day I tend not to weep over that I'm
Russian where I was I will tell you now
it's really not that complicated I got
red in my ledger I'd like to wipe it out
can you
can you wipe out that much red
drei coughs daughter Sao Paolo the
hospital fire
Barton told me everything the ledger is
dripping it's gushing red and you think
saving a man no more virtuous than
yourself will change anything this is
the basest sentimentality this is a
child prayer pathetic you lie and kill
in the service of liars and killers
you pretend to be separate to have your
own code something that makes up for the
horrors but they are part of you
and they will never go away I won't
touch Barton not until I make him kill
you slowly intimately in every way he
knows you fear and then her wake just
long enough to see his good work and
when he screams our split his skull
this is my bargain you mewling quim your
monster you hold the monster
so banner that's your play what
Loki means to unleash the Hulk keep
banner in the lab I'm on my way son Thor
is awful
thank you for your cooperation