If it's any comfort,
they died in their sleep.
Did you really think
I wanted more of you?
What the hell?
I'm grateful to them, though.
They brought you here.
Please, Captain.
The Soviets built
this chamber to withstand
the launch blast of UR-100 rockets.
I'm betting I could beat that.
Oh, I'm sure you could, Mr Stark.
Given time.
But then you'd never know
why you came.
You killed innocent people in Vienna
just to bring us here?
I've thought about
nothing else for over a year.
I studied you.
I followed you.
But now that you're standing here...
I just realised...
there's a bit of green
in the blue of your eyes.
How nice to find a flaw.
You're Sokovian.
Is that what this is about?
Sokovia was a failed state
long before you blew it to hell.
No.
I'm here because I made a promise.
You lost someone?
I lost everyone.
And so will you.
An empire toppled
by its enemies can rise again.
But one which crumbles from within?
That's dead.
Forever.
I know that road.
What is this?
Help my wife.
Please. Help.
Sergeant Barnes?
Howard!
No, Tony.
Did you know?
I didn't know it was him.
Don't bullshit me, Rogers.
Did you know?
Yes.