[Music]
I'm sorry that was odd
Thank You Thor you helped create this
I've had a vision a whirlpool that sucks
in all hope of life and how did Santa is
that what did yep the mind stone it's
one of the six Infinity stones the
greatest power in the universe
unparalleled in its destructive
capabilities then why would you bring
stock is right oh it's definitely the
end times
The Avengers cannot defeat Ultron not
alone why does your vision sound like
Jarvis we reconfigured Jarvis's matrix
to create something new I think I've had
my fill of new you think I'm a child of
Ultron you're not I'm not altering I'm
not Java silent I am
I looked in your head and saw
annihilation look again her silver
approval means Jack to me their powers
the horrors in our heads Ultron himself
they all came from the mind stone and
nothing compared to what it can unleash
the with it on our Tsar is it are you on
our side I don't think it's that simple
well better get real simple real soon I
am on the side of life Ultron isn't he
will end it all what's he waiting for
you
where sokovia he's gotten out there too
if we're wrong about you
if you're the monster that Ultron major
to be what what do you do
I don't want to kill hadron he's unique
and he's in pain but that pain will roll
over the earth so he must be destroyed
every form he's built every trace of his
presence on the net we have to act now
and not one of us can do it without the
others maybe I am a monster I don't
think I'd know if I were one and not
what you are and not what you intended
so there may be no way to make you trust
me but we need to go
right well done
three minutes yeah what you need
you