we'll never get it out now so certain
are you always with you it cannot be
done you nothing that I say master
moving stones around is one thing this
is totally different
no no different only different in your
mind you must unlearn what you have
there all right I'll give it a try
No why not do I'll do not there is no
try
I can't it's too big
sighs magic not look at me let me by my
size do you
hmm and where you should net for my Ally
is the force and Nepal for kite ISM
leads it makes it grow its energy
surrounds us and binds us luminous
beings are we not this crude matter you
must feel the force around you you treat
you me free blood everywhere
yes even between the ship
you weren't impossible
you
I don't believe it
neck is why you fail