I think lunchtime is but the worst time
of day for me always having to sit here
alone of course sometimes mornings
aren't so pleasant either waking up and
wondering if anyone would really miss me
if I never got out of bed
then there's the night too lying there
and thinking about all the stupid things
I've done during the day and all those
hours in between when I do all those
stupid things well lunch time is among
the worst times of the day for me well I
guess I'd better see what I've got
peanut butter some psychiatrists say
that people who eat peanut butter
sandwiches are lonely I guess the right
and when you're really lonely the peanut
butter sticks to the rule for your mouth
there's that cute little redheaded girl
eating your lunch over there I wonder
what she would do that went over and
asked her if I could sit and have lunch
with her she'd probably laugh right in
my face it's hard on a face when he gets
laughed in there's an empty place next
to her on the bench there's no reason
why I couldn't just go over and sit
there I could do that right now
all I have to do is stand up I'm
standing up
sitting down I'm a coward I'm so much of
a coward
she wouldn't even think of looking at me
she hardly ever does look at me in fact
I can't remember her ever looking at me
why shouldn't she look at me is there
any reason in the world why she
shouldn't look at me she's so great and
I'm so small that she can't spare one
little moment she's looking at me she's
looking at me you're thinking of that
other dress the one I wore to Lucinda's
party the one I'm talking about was the
very life blue one it had a design
embroidered around the waist
I don't remember something like this and
a skirt went out like this and had these
puffy sleeves and a sash like this oh
yes I remember yes well that was a dress
I was wearing last week when I met
Frieda and she told me she'd seen one
just like it over at that place on
lunchtime is among the worst times of
the day for me if that little redheaded
girl is looking at me with this stupid
bag over my head she must think I'm the
biggest fool alive but if she isn't
looking at me maybe I could take it off
quickly and she'd never notice it on the
other hand I can't tell if she's looking
until I take it off then again if I
never take it off I'll never have to
know if she was looking or not on the
other hand it's very hard to breathe it
here it's not looking at me
I wonder why she never looks at me oh
well another lunch hour over with only
2863 to