what happened did I paint what did he
leave us did he leave us any toys I know
I'm waiting with a great bumpkin when I
could have been out for trips or great
missed it you look at you got me up on
that ready with a great pumpkin and on a
game with a beagle I can get again to go
for Crystal cream and order your fault
I'll show what a fall I was I could have
had candy apples and gone I'm conky that
money also to thing but no I had to
listen to you you blockin what a fool I
was quicker tweets come only once a year
and I miss it by sitting in a pumpkin
patch with a blockhead you can you heard
about fury and a woman scorned haven't
you yes I guess I have well that's
nothing compared to the fury of a woman
who has been cheated out of tricks or
treats