look similar everything the light
touches is our kingdom
a king's time as ruler rises and falls
like the Sun one day Simba the Sun will
set on my time here and will rise with
you as the new king and this will all be
mine everything everything light touches
what about that shadowy place that's
beyond all borders must never go there
but I thought a king can do whatever he
want
oh this motor being king then getting
your way all the time there's more that
Simba
everything you see exists together in a
delicate balance as king we need to
understand that balance and respect all
the creatures from the crawling ant to
the leaping antelope dad don't we eat
the Antelope yes
Simba but let me explain when we die our
bodies become the grass and the Antelope
eat the grass and so we are all
connected in the great circle of life