big man in a suit of armor
take that off what are you genius
billionaire playboy philanthropist
what's it look like in there it seems to
run on some form of electricity mom
you're not wrong I won't touch Barton
not until I make him kill you slowly
intimately in every way he knows you
fear and then he'll wake just long
enough to see his good work and when he
screams I'll split his skull this is my
bargain you mewling quim cuz we can't
protect the Earth you can be damn well
sure we'll avenge it
how will your friends have time for me
when they're so busy fighting you
it's usually works well performance
issues you know not uncommon one out of
five director fury the council has made
a decision
I recognize the council has made a
decision but given that it's a
stupid-ass decision I've elected to
ignore it to when they come and they
will they'll come for you I have an army
we have a Hulk do not touch me again
then don't take my stuff you have no
idea what you're dealing with uh
Shakespeare in the Park doth smother no
you wear as her drapes
oh he's not leading an army from here I
don't think we should be focusing on
Loki that guy's brain is a bag full of
cats he could smell crazy on him
I've cared how you speak Loki's beyond
reason but he is of Asgard and he's my
brother
he killed 80 people in two days he's
adopted
dr. banner now might be a really good
time for you to get angry that's my
secret captain
I'm always angry get up you all of you
beneath me I am a god you dull creature
and I will not be bullied by puny God
you