when I was a kid I thought Zootopia was
this perfect place where everyone got
along and anyone could be anything
turns out real life's a little bit more
complicated than a slogan on a bumper
sticker
real life is messy we all have
limitations we all make mistakes
which means hey glass-half-full we all
have a lot in common and the more we try
to understand one another the more
exceptional each of us will be but we
have to try so no matter what type of
animal you are from the biggest elephant
to our first Fox
I implore you try
try to make the world a better place
look inside yourself and recognize that
change starts with you
it starts with me
it starts with all of us