[Music]
sorry
but if we make a little scotch
you
it's a key know much more better it is a
drawing of a key gentlemen what do
please do keys unlock things and
whatever this key unlocks inside there's
something valuable so we're setting out
to find whatever this key unlocks no we
don't have the key
we can't open whatever it is we don't
have that it unlocks so what purpose
would be served in planning would ever
need be unlocked which we don't have
without first having found the key one
so we're going after this key you're not
making any sense for any more questions
so we have a heading ah heading set sail
and I knew general
that way direction captain come on snap
doing like cellulitis
why is the rum always gone
you notice we say I'm glad to see you
Jack it's me will turn up I think Oh Ian
Dada UCP coming to let me down kill a
long I'm picky picky some means he wente
LUMS they say eunuch e60 Jack the
compass
that's all I need elizabeth is in danger
we were arrested for trying to help you
she faces the gallows makes a long ship
ship shots mommy long the sugar heavy
Bala Quila key what did you tell them
[Music]
underneath a boogie today you always
remember the day that you almost get
injected Ferro you want me to find it no
you want you to find this because the
finding of this finds you incapacity
really finding and or locating in your
discovering the detecting of a way to
save your dolly Bell hole was a place
yet this is a jar of death yes is a jar
of dirt going to hell if you do one deep
meaning bad get it head captain sparrow
come to join me cool and welcome aboard
let me have to find the man I love
I'm deeply flattered come but my first
and only love is the sea
meaning William Turner captain Sparrow
hide the wrong
my tremendous intuitiveness of the
female creature of all that you are
troubled I thought I'd be married by now
it good night you know busy I am captain
of a ship and being captain of a ship I
could in fact perform a very harsh right
here right on this deck thank you
why not we are very much alike you and I
I knew except for a sense of honor and
decency and a moral Center and personal
hygiene coming Haley come to negotiate I
have used why meet it look what I got
I got a drawer return I got a jar
dessert and guess what society
[Music]
you