when you marooned me on that godforsaken
spit of land you forgot one very
important thing mate I'm Captain Jack
Sparrow
oh no I'm picky picky
mum means he wheezy
once I say eunuch 860
why should I sail with any of you flora
we have tried to kill me in the past one
of you succeeded welcome to the
Caribbean left hey thanks
there's something hey Cheerilee have you
now very kind of you
but it would seem that as I possess a
ship and you don't you're the ones in
need of rescuing I'm not sure as I'm in
the mood I see my ship right there
can't spot it must be a tiny little
thing hiding somewhere behind a pearl
you are without doubt the worst pirate
but you have heard of me because you and
I are alike and they were coming there
when you had the chance to show it to do
the right thing I love those moments I
like to wave at them as they pass by
well that is a dinghy my vessel is
magnificent and fierce and huge fish why
then I confess it is my intention to
commandeer one of these ships pick up a
crew in Tortuga raid pillage plunder and
otherwise pill for my Weasley blackouts
out I seek no noise I think he's telling
the truth
if he was telling the truth he wouldn't
have told us unless of course he knew
you wouldn't believe the truth even if
he told it this is the day you always
remember is the day that you almost
getting Jack Sparrow made you captain
just giving the blood - you're not a
eunuch are you
ah
you may kill me but you may never insult
me Who am I Captain Jack Sparrow why is
the wrong guy
I'd the wrong shoot a man can understand
this shoot his tongue trim that scraggly
beard I'll tell you mate if every town
in the world will like this one a no man
would ever feel unwanted Gisele Amanda's
in there we don't have the key we can't
open whatever it is we don't have that
it unlocks so what purpose would be
served in finding would ever need be
unlock which we don't have without first
having found the key one losses so we're
going after this key you're not making
any sense fool mr. games
you miss remar hats like hike
I can get
if you were waiting for the opportune
moment that was is now if you'd be so
kind to be much of us if you drop me off
my ship full pardon commissioners our
drivers here on behalf of England and
the East India Trading Company as if I
could be bought for such a low price
ah Hector it's been too long hasn't it
I illegitimate I remember you shot me
Darden
on deck you scabrous dogs and surveys
bring me that horizon
and really bad eggs drink up me hearties
yo ho