[Music]
[Applause]
while it's so weird how you run into
people at the airport that's weird
definitely weird
hear me out Tony that doctor
psychiatrist he's behind all of this
captain
your highness anyway Ross gave me 36
hours to bring in that was 24 hours ago
can you help her brother out you're
after the wrong guy your judgment is to
secure your old war buddy killed
innocent people yesterday and there are
five more super soldiers just like Lee I
can't let the doctor find him first I
can't
he's you know what's about to happen do
you really want to punch your way out of
this one
all right I've run out of patience
underoos let's not kid thanks
well I couldn't stop the landing a
little better it's just a new suit what
eight something which is dark it's
perfect thank you yeah we don't really
need to start a conversation okay cap
captain big fan
spider-man yeah we'll talk about a
letter just everyone good job
you've been busy and you've been a
complete idiot dragon named Clint
rescuing Wanda from a place she doesn't
want to leave a safe place I'm trying to
keep you're trying to keep you from
turning the Avengers apart did that one
you say Arvid you're going to turn
Barnes over you going to come with us
now because it's us or squad a JSOC guys
with no compunction about being impolite
we've found it
the quinjets and hangar five North
runway
[Music]
alright Lang okay but what the hell is
that
believe this is yours Captain America
now great all right there's two on the
parking deck one of them's max mop I'm
Remy Robert produ you went to cap add to
anatomical Wilson and barn bondage Mike
you