was he married no there was a cellist I
think sorry
she looking good man you an idiot
why for believing for taking on Loki
alone he was doing his job he was I
believe should have waited
you should have sometimes there isn't a
way out Tony right I forgot before this
is the first time you lost a soldier we
are not soldiers I'm not Martin and
Fury's fight neither mine he's got the
same blood on his hand that Loki does
but right now we got to put that behind
us and get this done now Loki needs a
power source if we could put together a
legend at a personal that's not the
point that is the point that's Loki's
point he hit us all right where we live
why stairs apart Antonine conquers great
but he knows he has to take us out to
win right that's what it was to beat us
he wants to be seen doing it so what's
the audience Troy right I cut his act
understood guy yeah that's just previous
this is this is opening night and Loki
he's a full-tilt diva what flowers
what's parades monument built to the
skies with his name quest son bitch
[Music]
time to go go where I'll tell you on the
way can you fly one of those Jets I
can't
you got a suit
and sudo
[Music]
Oh
hey you guys aren't authorized to be in
here son just don't sir agent hill those
cards they were in Coulson's Locker
Lana's jacket
I needed to push you
[Music]
we have not authorized departure from
Maine they found it get our
communications back up whatever you have
to do I want eyes on everything
[Music]
you