I can't do this I know it's all wrong
but rights we shouldn't even be here
[Music]
we are
it's like in the great stories mr.
fertile the ones that really mattered
full of darkness and danger they were
and sometimes you didn't want to know
with yet because I'm to the end be happy
[Music]
how could the world go back to the way
it was when so much had happened
but in the end it's only a passing thing
this shadow even darkness must pass
every day will come and when the Sun
shines it will shine out the clearer
[Music]
those are the stories that stayed with
you at Mensa
even if you were too small to understand
why I think mr. farofa
I do understand I know no folk in those
stories had lots of chances of turning
back only they didn't they kept going
because they were holding on to
something what do we all belong to Sam
[Music]
but there's some good in this world mr.
Phil and it's worth fighting
[Music]
you