if you only knew the power of the dark
side obi-wan never told you what
happened the father he told me he told
me you killed no I am the father the son
of Skywalker must not become a Jedi if
he could be turned he would become a
powerful ally getting me done he will
join us or die Master
this station is now the ultimate power
in the universe I suggest we use it
don't be too proud of this technological
terror you've constructed the ability to
destroy a planet is insignificant next
to the power of the force you don't know
the power of the dark side I must obey
my master I will not turn and you'll be
forced to kill me
if that is your destiny your sad
devotion to that ancient religion has
not helped you conjure up the stolen
data tapes or given you clairvoyance
enough to find the rebels hidden fort I
find your lack of faith disturbing
you are unwise to know your defenses you
have failed me for the last time captain
Piett yes ma'am
make ready to land our troops beyond
their energy field and deploy the feet
so the nothing gets off the system you
are in the math now Admiral yet I can
only I've been waiting for you
we meet again at last the circle is
nothing when I left you I was but to
learn now I am the master only a master
of evil nada
[Music]
obi-wan is talking whether you have
controlled your fear now release your
anger only your hatred you can destroy
me you can destroy the Emperor he has
four scenes it is your destiny join me
and together we can rule the galaxy as
father and son