a Jedi uses the force for knowledge and
defense never attack but tell me why I
kill no there is no way nothing more
will I teach you today clear your mind
of question go with the Queen to Naboo
and discover the identity of this dark
warrior this is the clue we need to
unravel the mystery of the synth may the
force be with you
[Music]
then I am a Jedi not yet one thing
remains Vader you must confront Vader
death is a natural part of life rejoice
for those around you who transform into
the force mourn them do not miss them do
not train yourself to let go of
everything you fear to lose fear is the
path to the dark side fear leads to
anger anger leads to hate hate leads to
suffering
[Music]
I sense much fear in you master moving
stones around is one thing this is
totally different
no no different only different in your
mind you must unlearn what you have
Pierre all right I'll give it a try no
final do
[Music]
around the survivors a perimeter create
it's too big tires make a net look at me
that'd be my size do you
hmm and where you should not for my Ally
is the force and the powerful kite is
anger fear pleasure the dark side what
you start down the dark path forever
will it dominate your destiny
the boy you trained ganya is consumed by
Darth Vader but do not know where the
emperor has sent him use your feelings
obi-wan and find him you will
you