okay now I realize that you guys you
probably heard about this other villain
who's all the pyramids apparently it's a
big deal people are calling it the crime
of the century and stuff like that
what am I upset no I am NOT a little but
we have had a pretty good year ourselves
and you guys are all right in my bottle
no no racist yeah I'm going to get any
losses why did we do well we stole the
Time Square jumbo
but this level we stole the Statue of
Liberty
the small ones from Las Vegas I won't
even mention the Eiffel Tower also be ok
I wasn't going to tell you about this
yet but I have been working on something
very big something that you all this
pyramid thing out of the water and
thanks to the efforts of my good friend
dr. Nefario thank you
now we have located a shrink-ray in a
secret lab and once we take this Sri
clay we will have the capability to pull
off the throne of the century we are
going to steal
like wait I haven't told you what it is
hey Dave listen up please
next we are going to steal
you