and now an exclusive sneak preview of
DreamWorks Animation's new movie
Penguins of Madagascar
Antarctica an inhospitable wasteland but
even here on the Earth's frozen button
we find life and not just any life
penguins enjoy a sub frolicking madly
cute and cuddly laughs look at them
tumbling onto their chubby bonbons who
could take these risks to little snow
clowns
seriously does anyone even know where
we're marching to nothing me to fly to
the front of the line and see for
ourselves
cool ski Rica engage aerial surveillance
we appear to be flightless well what's
the point of these Oh
like hey this could be ours hey what are
you cold let's call it the high one hey
anybody see that
that's an A you know we lose a few eggs
every year it's just nature you know
what
I reject nature who's with me
the old ship
no one's ever returned from there alive
relax Kowalski there's a bird down there
now he's fine leopard seals nature's
snakes aren't snakes nature snakes
how should I know live on the flippin
frozen tundra they're going for the egg
give me a way down there ASAP all one
would have to do is collect 300 feet of
kelp dried in a tiny and helpless the
baby penguins are frozen with fear they
know if they fall from this cliff they
will surely die
Gupta give him a shot harnessing the
jellyfish we've trained to obey simple
voice commands
okay I guess that works
do we see the white of it sighs rustling
Gimpo very little white almost not it
gotta have a little bit of white right
none whatsoever
what if they look really far to the left
Walski analysis we are really awesome at
this i won oh my bad moment but
extraordinary beauty exact in my mouth
hello are you my family
you don't have a family and we're all
going to die what-mon I thought that was
what we were all nothing about no one's
gonna die no you've got kid
you've got us we've got each other
that ain't a family I don't know what is
what's our trajectory 95 percent certain
we're still doomed and the other 5%
adventuring glory like no Penguins have
ever seen before
I'll take that action discover the
untold story of how four brothers became
DreamWorks Penguins of Madagascar