inner peace
Master Shifu hey Master Shifu where we
got pirates vandals of volcano Mountain
whatever it is I will take them down cuz
I am in a mood I need to get something
done you know what I mean uh what are
you doing one of that's true ways final
teachings
Wow awesome how did you do that inner
peace inner peace that's cool
inner peace of what it is the next phase
of your training every master must find
his path to inner peace some choose to
meditate for 50 years in a cave just
like this without the slightest taste of
food or water or some find it through
pain and suffering as I did both the day
you were chosen as Dragon Warrior was
the worst day of my life by far nothing
else came close it was the worst most
painful mind destroying horrible moment
okay I have ever experienced but once I
realized the problem was not you but
within me I found inner peace and was
able to harness the flow of the universe
so that's it I just need inner peace my
innards are already super super peaceful
so all I need to do is just get this
thing going
inner peace you're going down now show
me what you were doing there with your
feet