master master hmm I have it it's up it's
very bad news uh Shifu there is just
news there is no good or bad master your
vision your vision was right Tai Lung
has broken out of prison he's on his way
that is bad news if you do not believe
that the Dragon Warrior can stop him the
Panda master that Panda is not the
Dragon Warrior he wasn't even meant to
be here
it was an accident there are no
accidents
yes I know you've said that already
twice well that was no accident i de
thrush I our friend the Panda will never
fulfill his destiny no you yours until
you let go of the illusion of control
illusion yes look at this tree seafood I
cannot make it blossom when it suits me
no make it bear fruit before its time
but there are things we can't control I
can control when the fruit will fall I
can control yeah where to plant the seed
hyah
that is no illusion master ah yes but no
matter what you do that seed will grow
to be a peach tree you may wish for an
apple or an orange but you will get a
peach but a peach cannot defeat Tai Lung
maybe it can if you are willing to guide
it to nurture it to believe in it
but how how I need your help master no
you just need to believe
promise me Shifu promise me you will be
thief I I will try good
my time has come
you must continue your journey without
me what what what are you what
aye sir
you can't leave me
you must believe
master