I see you have found a sacred peach tree
of Evan Lewis de Meaux
is that what this is I am so sorry I
gotta whiz like a regular people tree I
understand you eat when you are upset Oh
sir I'm not upset
why don't worry I will miss Ethan Gaza
so why are you upset ah I probably
sucked more today than anyone in the
history of kung-fu in the history of
China in the history of sucking probably
and the five man you should have seen
him they totally hate me
totally how is she forever gonna turn me
into the Dragon Warrior
I mean I'm not like the five I've got no
claws no wings no venom even mantis has
those thingies ah maybe I should just
quit and go back to making noodles
quit don't quit noodles don't noodles
you are too concerned with what was and
what will be is a saying yesterday is
history
tomorrow is a mystery but today is a
gift that is why it is called present