there will be no foolish wand-waving or
silly incantations in this class as such
I don't expect many of you to appreciate
the subtle science and exact art that is
potion making however for those select
few who possess the predisposition I can
teach you how to bewitch the mind and
ensnare the senses I can tell you how to
bottle fame brew glory and even put a
stopper in death then again maybe some
of you have come to Hogwarts in
possession of abilities so formidable
that you feel confident enough to not
pay attention
mr. Potter our new celebrity tell me
what would I get if I added powdered
root of asphodel to an infusion of
wormwood you don't know well let's try
again where mr. Potter would you look at
if I asked you to find me a bezoar I
don't know sir
and what is the difference between
monkshood and wolfbane I don't know sir
petty clearly Fame isn't everything is
it mr. Potter