secretary Ross has a Congressional Medal
of Honor which is one more than you have
so let's say we agree to this thing
how long is it going to be before they
LoJack us like a bunch of common
criminal 117 countries want to sign this
117 Sam and you're just like now it's
cool which I'm longer you're gonna play
both I have an equation oh now this will
clear it up in the eight years since
mrs. Stark announced himself as iron man
the number of known enhanced persons has
grown exponentially and during the same
period the number of potentially
world-ending events has risen at a
commensurate rate these things our fault
I'm saying there may be a causality our
very strength invites challenged
challenged incites conflict conflict
breeds catastrophe oversight
oversight is not an idea that can be
dismissed out of hand boom
Tony you're being uncharacteristically
non hyper-verbal because he's already
made up his mind oh you know me so long
actually I'm nursing an electromagnetic
headache that's what's going on cabs
just pain discomfort
who's putting coffee grounds in the
disposal my rent a bed and breakfast for
the biker gang
oh that's Charles Spencer by the way
it's a great kid computer engineering
degree 3.6 GPA at a floor-level gig and
intel plan for the fall but first i'm
going to put some miles on his soul
before he parked it behind a desk see
the world maybe be of service
Charlie don't want to go to Vegas for
Fort Lauderdale which is what I would do
we didn't go to Paris or Amsterdam
sounds fun he decided to spend his
summer building sustainable housing for
the poor des with sokovia he want to
make a difference I suppose I mean we
won't know because we drop it building
on them while we were kicking ass
there's no decision-making process here
we need to be put in check whatever form
that takes I'm game if we can't accept
limitations we're bound realist for no
better than the bad guys
Sony someone dies on your watch you
don't keep up who said we're giving up
we offer not taking responsibility for
our actions
this document just shifts the blind
sorry Steve that that is dangerously
arrogant this is the United Nations
we're talking about it's not the world
Security Council it's not shield it's
not hide milk but it's run by people
with agendas and agendas change that's
good that's why I'm here when I realized
what my weapons were capable of in the
wrong hands I shut it down stop
manufacturing you chose to do that if we
sign this we surrender our right to
choose what if this panel sends us some
what we don't think we should do what if
there somewhere we need to go and they
don't let us we may not be perfect to
save his hands are still our own if we
don't do this now it's gonna be done to
us later that's the fact that won't be
pretty saying they'll come for me we
would protect you maybe Tony's right if
we have one hand on the wheel we can
still clear taking aren't you the same
woman who told the government to kiss
her ass a few years ago I'm just reading
a terrain we have made some very public
mistakes we need to win their trust back
focus up I'm sorry did I just miss hear
you or did you agree miss uh I want to
take it back no no no you can't
retracted thank you
we precedented okay case closed
I win
Aska
you