so the mark 7 is not ready for
deployment then skip the spinning rims
were on the clock
please tell me you're going to appeal to
my humanity actually I'm planning to
threaten you you should have left your
honor on for that ya seen a bit of
mileage and you've got the little stick
of destiny
you like a drink extolling me right
change anything
no no threatening no drink you sure I'm
having one that's atari a-- coming
nothing will change that
what have I to fear the Avengers that's
what we call ourselves sort of like a
team
Earth's Mightiest Heroes timeframe yes
I've met them yeah
tix as well to get any traction I'll
give you that one but let's do a head
count here
your brother the demigod a super soldier
living legend who kind of lives up to
the legend a man with breathtaking
anger-management issues a couple of
Master assassins and you big fella
you've managed to piss off every single
one of them that was the plan
not a great plan when they come
and they will I'll come for you I have
an army we have a Hulk well I thought
the Beast had one at all you're missing
the point there's no throne there is no
version of this where you come out on
top maybe your army comes and maybe it's
too much for us but it's all on you if
we can't protect the air if you can be
damn well sure we'll avenge it
how would your friends have time for me
when they're so busy fighting you it's
usually works well performance issues
not uncommon one out of five Jarvis and
it turned out you all fall before me boy
yeah
you
and there's one other person you pissed
off his name is Phil