in America's on threat one concern
doctor you're on that list shooting
above or below record stocks herbal
threat I feel friendship respect fun mm
Pat's point six six Bravo
these are likely from Tubbs bachelor
Peter Bonanno do your log what is your
haul over arms damn you Nisshin Oh
speak of control yet you caught chaos
this is mo isn't it no what are we a
team no no we're a chemical mixture that
makes chaos where we're at time bomb you
need to step away
I shouldn't the guy let off a little
steam you know damn well why back off
I'm starting to want you to make me big
man in a suit of armor
take that off what are you genius
billionaire playboy philanthropist I
know guys with none of that worth Kenny
you I've seen the footage the only thing
you really fight for is yourself you're
not the guy to make the sacrifice play
to lay down on a wire or let the other
guy crawl over you I think I would just
cut the wire
always a way out you know you may not be
a threat but you better stop pretending
to be a hero a hero like you you're a
laboratory experiment Rogers everything
special about you came out of a bottle
put on the suit let's go a few rounds
you people are so petty
and tiny yeah agent Romanoff would you
escort dr. banner back to his where you
rent in my room the cell was just in
case you needed to kill me but you can't
I know I tried I got low and then seemed
in so I put a bullet in my mouth and the
other guys spit it out so I moved on I
focused on helping other people I was
good until you dragged me back into this
freak show and put everyone here at risk
you want to know my secret agent
Romanoff if you want to know how I stay
calm
you better
but unsaid
got it sorry kids you don't get to see
my party trick after all located the
tesseract I could get there fast test
rocks belongs on Asgard no human is a
mouthful you're not going alone here
stop me put on the suit let's find out
I'm not afraid to hit man put on the
suit oh my god
you