take hydrogen you add oxygen you burn
now I have hundreds of liters of unused
hydrazine at the MDV if I run the
hydrazine over an Iridium catalyst it'll
separate into n2 and h2 and then if I
just direct the hydrogen into a small
area and burn it luckily in the history
of humanity nothing bad has ever
happened from gliding hydrogen on fire
NASA hates fire because of the whole
fire makes everybody die in space thing
so everything they sent us up here with
his flames argued with the notable
exception of Martinez's personal items
I am sorry Martinez but if you didn't
want me to go through your stuff you
should know left me for dead on a
desolate planet by the way I'm figuring
you're going to be fine with this given
my present situation counting on you
so yeah I blew myself up best guess
I forgot to account for the excess
oxygen
I've been exhaling I did my calculations
because I'm stupid
I'm gonna get back to work here just as
soon as my ears stop ringing interesting
side note this is actually how the jet
propulsion lab was founded five guys at
Caltech trying to make rocket fuel and
they nearly burned down their dorm and
rather than expel them banished them to
a nearby farm told him to keep working
now we have a space program okay