as walnut date lobes go
that wasn't bad so what do we have here
Richard Tech huh fish store Salvation
Army garbage I your dumpster diver yeah
I was anyway look um I definitely did
not apply for your glory huh me first a
quick question of the torkoal variety
that's cute
right um no what do you what do you look
at you go wow nice catch 3,000 pounds 40
miles an hour
it's not easy got mad skills that's all
that's all on YouTube though right
I mean that's when you found it because
you know that's not fake it's all done
on a computer I liked that video yeah
yeah yeah oh you mean like those UFOs
over Phoenix so do this spider wing
crime-fighting spider or spider boy
spider-man not in that onesie or not
it's not a onesie believe this I was
actually having a really good day today
you know start didn't miss my train his
perfectly good DVD player was just
sitting there and algebra test nailed it
who else knows anybody well my not even
your unusually attractive him no no no
no no if she knew she'd freak out and
when she freaks out I freaked out you
know what I think it's really cool this
wedding tensile strength is off the
charts
i manufactured that I did climbing walls
are you doing that he said gross a long
story I was already can you even see in
the yes yes I can't I can't see in those
okay it's just that when whatever
happened happened it's like my senses
have been dialed to 11 there's there's
way too much input so they use kind of
help me focus you in dire need of an
upgrade systemic top to bottom 100 point
restoration that's why I'm here why are
you doing this I gotta know what's your
mo what gets you out of that twin bed in
the morning because
because I've been me my whole life and
I've had these powers for six months I
read books I build computers and yeah I
would love to play football but I
couldn't then so I shouldn't matter
because you're different exactly but I
can't tell anybody that so I'm not look
when you can do the things that I can
but you don't
and then the bad things happen they have
to look at you so you want to look after
the little guy you want to do your part
make the world a better place on that
right yeah yeah yeah just looking up a
little
I'm gonna sit here so you move the leg
jump a sport no I don't I don't even
have a driver been to Germany No oh
you'll love it I can't go to Germany
why pretend you didn't say that
I'm being serious I can't just drop out
of smoke a little dangerous so haughty
I'm taking this trip don't tell me all
right Spyder
[Music]
sorry I'll get
you