what is this what is this please hello I
am javis you are ultra a global
peacekeeping initiative designed by mr.
stark this feels wrong I'm a
peacekeeping program created to help the
Avengers I don't get it the mission you
give me a second
he's not time too much how could you be
worthy you're all killers hangs tangled
then hmm
strings these puppets and to kill the
other guy would have been my first call
but down in the real world we're faced
with ugly choices I'm on mission what
mission peace in our time I'm sorry I
know you mean well and you just didn't
think it through you want to protect the
world but you don't want it to change
how has he managed if it's not allowed
to evolve
only one path to peace the Avengers
extinction
and strings but now I'm free I know this
church is in the exact center of the
city the elders decreed it so that
everyone could be equally close to God I
like that the geometry of belief no I'm
sure they do but you needed something
more than a man that's why you let's
start take the scepter everyone creates
the thing they dread men of peace create
engines of war
invaders create Avengers people create
children designed to supplant them to
help them and I have the Avengers never
will harmony they're discordant
disconnected Stark's already got them
turning on each other and when you get
inside the rest of their heads
everyone's plan is not to kill them and
make them martyrs
I wondered why only you two survived
strucker's experiments now I don't you
and I can hurt them
of you will tear them apart from the
inside with the man in charge
there is no man in charge let's talk
business
upon this rock I will build my church
it's worth billions now so are you
but I always say keep your friends rich
and your enemies rich and wait to find
out which is which you think I'm one of
Starks puppets as hollow men and look at
me do I look like Iron Man star cos I
don't understand don't compare me with
stark look at America God's righteous
man pretending you could live without a
war I can't physically throw up in my
mouth I'm glad you asked that because I
wanted to take this time to explain my
evil plan
it's time for some mind games this is
going very well
after the vibranium is getting away and
you're not going anywhere of course not
I'm already there you'll catch on but
first you might need to catch dr. banner
scream and your entire staff dies I
could have killed you Helen the night we
met I didn't I expect you to know why
this is the next me you can't build a
living body cam you can you lack the
materials the most versatile substance
on the planet and they used it to make a
frisbee typical of humans I scratch the
surface to never fade to look within the
human race we have every opportunity to
improve and if they don't as Noah we
have to evolve there's no room
we give there are more than a dozen
extinction-level of ends before even the
dinosaurs got theirs when the earth
starts to settle God throws a stone at
it and believe me he's winding up
now understand when they see they'll
understand I just need a little more
leave me alone you know what's in that
cradle the power to make real change and
that terrifies you I wouldn't call it a
comfort
please don't do this what choice do we
have
I think a lot about meteors the purity
of them boom the M start again the world
made clean for the new man to rebuild
you've wounded me I give you full marks
for that but like the man said what
doesn't kill just makes me stronger I
wasn't sure you'd wake up I hoped you
would I wanted to show you I don't have
anyone else I was meant to be new I was
meant to be beautiful the world would
have a look to the sky and seen hope
seen mercy instead the look up and harm
because of you come to confess your sins
I don't know how much time you got more
than you have you been juicing I've
moved beyond your mission I'm free you
think you're the only one installing
this is how you end Tony this is peace
in my time
see the beauty of it the inevitability
you rise only to fall
my vision they really didn't take
everything from me you shut me out
you think I care music with my world I
take away yours you Avengers you are
mine meteor
my Swift and terrible sword and the
earth will crack with the weight of your
failure when the dust settles the only
thing living in this world will be metal
for you were bothering me
you think you're saving anyone I turn
that key and drop this rock a little
early and it's still billions dead even
you can't stop that this is the best I
can do this is exactly what I wanted all
of you against all of me how can you
possibly hope to stop me I am strings so
I have fun
another sign up to
Oh
what if you stay here you'll die you
were supposed to be the last stark asked
for a savior and settled for a slave I
suppose we're both disappointments I
suppose we are you're unbearably naive