my name's Ralph and I'm a bad guy let's
see I'm nine feet tall I weigh 643
pounds got a little bit of a temper on
me my passion bubble is very near the
surface I guess I'm not gonna lie
anyhoo what else I'm a wrecker I wrecked
things professionally I mean I'm very
good at what I do probably the best I
know the thing is fixing is the name of
the game literally fix-it Felix jr.
so yeah naturally the guy with the name
fix-it Felix is the good guy he's nice
enough his good guys go definitely fix
his stuff really well but if you've got
a magic hammer from your father how hard
can it be if he was a regular contractor
carpenter guy I guarantee you you would
not be able to fix the damage that I do
as quickly when Felix does a good job he
gets a medal but are their medals for
wrecking stuff really well to that I say
ha and no there aren't
thirty years of in doing this and I've
seen a lot of other games come and go
kind of sad
think about all those guys from
asteroids boom gone
centipede who knows where that guy is
you know look a steady arcade gig is
nothing to sneeze ax
I'm very lucky it's just I gotta say it
becomes kind of hard to love your job
when no one seems to like you for doing
I'll clear the arcades close sure you
can
oooh what a day so you want to head to
tappers ken have your buying buddy
ah maybe I wouldn't be feeling this way
if things were different after work but
it is what it is Felix and the nice
Landers go hang out in their homes which
is just fixed and everyone you know they
go to their homes I go to mine which
happens to be a dump and when I say a
dump I don't mean like a shabby place I
mean an actual dump the garbage goes and
a bunch of bricks and smash building
parts that's that's what I call home I
guess I can't Billy ate too much I got
my bricks I got my stump
it looks uncomfortable it's actually
fine I'm good but if I'm really honest
with myself I see Felix up there getting
patted on the back people giving him pie
thanking him so happy to see him all the
time
some time to think man sure must be nice
being the good guy